class QuizQuestionUnit2 {
  int id;
  String question;
  List options;
  int correctAns;

  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      {required this.id,
      required this.question,
      required this.options,
      required this.correctAns});
}

List questionListUnit2 = [
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 1,
      question:
          "1)	On increasing the temperature, the conductance of a solution",
      options: ["Decreases", "Increases", "Remains constant", "None of above"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 2,
      question: "The law of electrolysis was given by",
      options: ["Newton", "Faraday", "Arrhenius", "Ostwald"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 3,
      question:
          "pH-metric Titration of SASB used to determine the unknown concentration of",
      options: ["Strong Acid", "Weak Acid", "Salt ", "None of above"],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 11,
      question: "At infinite dilution equivalent conductance is ",
      options: ["Minimum", "Maximum", "Zero", "None"],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 12,
      question:
          "Membrane used in fluoride selective electrode is made up of _____",
      options: ["LaF3", "La(OH)3", "NaOH", "NaCl"],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 13,
      question:
          "The boundary potential across the membrane gets developed due to the ____ in the concentration of ions",
      options: ["difference", "decrease", "increase", "Constant"],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 14,
      question: "As H+ ion concentration decreases, EMF of the cell______",
      options: ["Decreases", "Increases", "Remains zero", "Remains constant "],
      correctAns: 2),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 15,
      question: "Unit of Equivalent conductance is ---",
      options: ["mhos cm-1", "S cm-1", "mhos", "None of the above  "],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 16,
      question: "HgHgCl2 ,  KCl (saturated)	is representation of_____",
      options: [
        "Calomel electrode",
        "SHE",
        "Ag-AgCl electrode",
        "Glass electrode "
      ],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 17,
      question:
          "In conductivity cell a pair of platinum electrodes are coated with_____",
      options: [
        "Platinum chloride",
        "KCl",
        "Silver chloride",
        "Platinum black  "
      ],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 18,
      question: "The calomel electrode is made from which of the following",
      options: ["ZnCl2", "CuCl2", "HgCl2", "Hg2Cl2"],
      correctAns: 4),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 19,
      question: "Distance between electrodes in a conductivity cell",
      options: [
        "Is kept fixed",
        "Can be altered ",
        "Alters as reaction proceeds ",
        "None of these",
      ],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 20,
      question:
          "Titration curve of conductometric titration consist of two intersecting lines the intersection point is known as______",
      options: [
        "Conductivity point",
        "Break curve point",
        "End point",
        "None of the above "
      ],
      correctAns: 3),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 21,
      question:
          "The advantage of potentiometric titration is that it can be used for titration of",
      options: [
        "calcium salt solutions",
        "charcoal solutions",
        "colored solutions",
        "calomel solutions "
      ],
      correctAns: 3),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 22,
      question:
          "A plot of measured Ecell as a function of titrant in Potentiometric redox titration of 1:1 mole ratio is ___",
      options: ["S shaped", "T shaped", "V shaped", "L shaped"],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 23,
      question:
          "In potentiometric titrations, as pH of the solution increases , EMF of the cell",
      options: ["Increases", "Decreases", "Remains zero", "Remains constant "],
      correctAns: 1),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 24,
      question: "In electromagnetic wave, reciprocal of wavelength is",
      options: ["Frequency", "Velocity", "Wave number", "Amplitude "],
      correctAns: 3),
  QuizQuestionUnit2(
      id: 25,
      question: "The solution of pH 7 signifies",
      options: [
        "Pure solution",
        "Neutral solution",
        "Neutral solution",
        "Acidic solution "
      ],
      correctAns: 2),
];
